http://pokerrpg.com/privacy.php

PRIVACY POLICY
This statement was last updated July 24, 2006.
1. Collecting your Personal Information
The information we collect from you is only for the purpose of use of the member services such as the forums and actual gameplay. This information is limited to e-mail address, name, country, age, and other various information. You will always be fully informed to why you are giving over such information.
2. Use of your Personal Information
We use your personal information for two primary purposes:
To make the site easier for you to use by not making you enter your personal information more than once.
To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you.
PokerRPG will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on PokerRPG or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of PokerRPG, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of PokerRPG, its Web site, or the public.
3. Control of your Personal Information
When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, PokerRPG will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.
4. Security of your Personal Information
PokerRPG strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.
Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country where PokerRPG, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located.
You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your username and password, so do not share these with others.
5. Use of Cookies
Cookies will be placed on your computer by PokerRPG only for login and gameplay purposes. Cookies will never be placed on your computer by third parties. A cookie must be set to keep you logged into your account by holding account information that is essential for the login process.
6. Changes to this Statement
PokerRPG will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this Statement.
7. Contact Information
PokerRPG welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy, please contact us by e-mail.
© 2006-2019 PokerRPG & GoldFire Studios, Inc.
Terms / Privacy / Twitter / Facebook / Extras
